SULEIDIS LEYVA

QA ANALYST

Phone: +598 947 149 09 - Mail: suleidisdanai@gmail.com - <u>linkedin.com/in/suleidis-leyva-ramirez</u>

QA with 1+ years of experience in manual testing, ensuring quality and functionality in agile environments (Scrum, Kanban). Expert in test design and execution (functional, regression, exploratory, smoke) and defect management using Jira and Azure DevOps. Strong attention to detail, analytical thinking, and continuous improvement focus to ensure reliable and efficient products.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ANF AC Autoridad de Certificación - Madrid España

2023 - Present

Junior QA Analyst

- Requirements analysis and acceptance criteria for test planning.
- Design and execution of test cases, ensuring coverage and quality.
- Execution of functional tests (verification, regression, exploratory, API, smoke, sanity and Ad Hoc testing).
- Reporting and tracking defects found during test execution and exploratory sessions.
- SQL database validation to check integrity, consistency, relationships, and business rules.
- API Testing with Postman
- Updating documentation and proposing quality process improvements.

Up Work - Tester Work 2022-2023

Independent Software Tester

- Execution of user acceptance testing (UAT) and beta testing on various applications.
- User experience (UX) validation to improve usability and interaction.
- Reporting defects with clear and detailed documentation.
- Cross-browser testing and responsiveness validation across different devices using BrowserStack and DevTools.
- Collaboration with clients to optimize product quality.

TOOLS AND SKILLS

- Manual QA
- Jira (Zephy || Xray)
- Azure DevOps
- Redmine
- Trello
- Postman

- Agile Methodologies
 Scrum and Kanban
- English B1+
- GitHub
- Visual Studio Code
- Html CSS -JavaScript

- DevTools Chrome
- DevTools Firefox
- WAVE (Accessibility)
- Lighthouse Performance & Accessibility)
- Browserstack

EDUCATION

Web Development - (JAP) Jóvenes a Programar por Ceibal Uruguay 2023-2024

Professional Software Tester - Edutin Accademy 2022-2023

Technical High School Degree - Holguín Cuba 2008-2013